Nothing can stop you from falling in love
The World Unseen is a romance, drama film directed by Shamim Sarif.
A drama centered on two women who engage in a dangerous
relationship during South Africa's apartheid era.
Miriam, played by Lisa Ray.
Amina Harjan, played by Sheetal Sheth.
Omar, played by Parvin Dabas.
Rehmat, played by Nandana Sen.
Jacob, played by David Dennis.
Madeleine, played by Grethe Fox.
The World Unseen is a 2007 historical romantic drama film, written and
directed by Shamim Sarif, adapted from her own novel.
The film is set in 1950s Cape Town, South Africa
during the beginning of apartheid.
The film stars Lisa Ray and Sheetal Sheth as two Indian South African women
who fall in love in a racist, sexist, and homophobic society.
Ray and Sheth also star together in another Shamim Sarif movie, I
Can't Think Straight, released in November 2008.
The World Unseen was made with the assistance of the National Film and Video
Foundation of South Africa, which took a minority equity stake in the film.
The film explores themes of racial segregation, lesbian
relationship, male homosexuality, woman director, lesbian.
The tone is emotional.